RIZKI NABIL AUFA

Bekasi, ID | +62 82112776194 | rizki.nbl123@gmail.com | rizkinabil.github.io | linkedin.com/in/rizkinabilaufa

SUMMARY

Recently graduated Bachelor of Computer Science with a passion for product development and software engineering. Have an experience in full-stack web development and collaborating with diverse teams to deliver user-centered products. Committed to enhancing product excellence and making a positive impact.

EDUCATION

TELKOM UNIVERSITY

Bandung, ID 2019 - 2023

Bachelor's Degree

Major in Computer Science;

Cumulative GPA: 3.68/4.0;

Relevant Coursework: Algorithms; Data Structures; Database; Object-Oriented Programming; Human Computer Interface; Software Engineering; Data Science; Artificial Intelligence; Machine Learning;

EXPERIENCE

LEAP TELKOM DIGITAL - PT TELEKOMUNIKASI INDONESIA

Bandung (Hybrid), ID

- INS (Digital Infrastructure & Security)

Jul 2022 – Jun 2023

Full-stack Developer Intern

- Assisted in developing and maintaining responsive web applications using React Typescript material design from minimal-ui-kit.
- Contributed to the optimization of database schemas, queries, and data models on Hasura GraphQl.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams, including designers and product managers, to deliver high-quality solutions and adaptive design.

- AGREE

Frontend Web Developer Intern

- Responsible for developing, testing, and collaborating with other developer teams.
- Helped the team to achieve a rapid innovation target before launched in Netherlands with total 4 sprint development.
- Learned and practiced Web Platform development, unit testing, and best practice from Senior web developer (Nextjs, Redux, jest)

HIMPUNAN MAHASISWA INFORMATIKA TELKOM UNIVERSITY

Bandung, ID

Head of Internal Department

Apr 2022 – Mar 2023

- This Department focused on maintaining and improve good relations in the internal major of Infromatics at Telkom University
- Responsible to supervise three divisions under this department, there are Intra Kampus, Akademik, and Kemahasiswaan division
- · Create a new work program innovation that is implemented this year

Intra Kampus Division

Aug 2021 – Jan 2022

- Staff of Intra Kampus Division, responsible for maintaining internal relations between the associations in Telkom University
- Led a team to implement e-sport competition that intended for the Students Association in Telkom University.
- Achieve the success parameters in every work program in this division

ASE LABORARTORY Bandung, ID

Frontend Web Developer

Jun 2021 - March 2022

- ASE (Advanced Software Engineering) Laboratory is one of Laboratory in Telkom University focused on Software Engineering.
- Create a Voting web application. I'm working on a project as a frontend web developer.
- Gaining and learning more knowledge about web development in software engineering

PROJECTS

RIZKI NABIL - WEBSITE

April 2021

- Designed and implemented a personal website using Bootstrap in 1 day.
- Enabled users know more about me by showing my personal project and portofolios.
- Responsive web app that enable user to experience the web depending on the size of the screen.
- Utilized: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, nodeJS, Bootstrap.

FINGERVOTE - WEBSITE

July 2021

- Implemented a Voting web application using Vue. Is in 3 months.
- FingerVote is a Web-based application that can be used for online voting.
- Worked in a team of 3 people as a Frontend developer, Backend developer, and UI/UX designer.
- Utilized: VueJs, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Consuming API with Axios.

MOOVIEW – WEBSITE April 2022

- Designed and implemented a movie list recommendation using Nuxt.js in 2 days.
- Consumed TMDB API for the movie data recommendation and used PWA optimization.
- Enabled users to view a movie recommendation by the genre or categories.
- Utilized: Nuxt.js, Vuetify, Figma, TMDB API, JavaScript.

DEVENTORY - WEBSITE

Mei 2022

- Designed and Implemented a Front-end development tools portal using Nuxt.js in 2 weeks.
- Using GraphQl for data mutations and querying.
- Enabled users to see web tools references for front-end development tools.
- Utilized: Nuxt is, custom bootstrap style (scss), GraphQL

POINTS ID - WEBSITE

Jul 2022

- Implemented a loyalty point agent website (frontend) using Nuxt.js in 3 months.
- Create dashboard admin for managing and controlling the cashflow.
- Enabled users to exchange their loyalty points for variant products.
- Utilized: Nuxt js, vuetify, chart js.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Upper Intermediate in JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Python, Java, SQL, basic typescript

Frameworks: React, Vue, NodeJS, Express, Nuxt.js, Next.js

Developer Tools: Git, React, SASS, Testing Library, GraphQL

Relevant Skills: Web Performance, Web Accessibility, Clean Code, Software Testing

Certifications & Training: Vue.js: Learning the basics by building a movie web app (Udemy), Full-stack JavaScript/MERN Developer (BWA), Understand everything about Vue.js (MSIB), Program Magang Mahasiswa Bersertifikat / Kampus Merdeka – PT.Telekomunikasi Indonesia